{
  "date": "2025-09-04",
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "city_for_team",
      "question": "In which city do the Suns play (NBA)?",
      "options": [
        "Philadelphia",
        "Orlando",
        "Sacramento",
        "Phoenix"
      ],
      "answer": "Phoenix",
      "meta": {
        "league": "NBA",
        "team": "Suns"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "division_for_team",
      "question": "In which division do the Falcons play (NFL)?",
      "options": [
        "NFC South",
        "AFC South",
        "AFC East",
        "NFC East"
      ],
      "answer": "NFC South",
      "meta": {
        "league": "NFL",
        "team": "Falcons"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "team_for_city",
      "question": "Which MLB team plays in Houston?",
      "options": [
        "Royals",
        "Astros",
        "White Sox",
        "Phillies"
      ],
      "answer": "Astros",
      "meta": {
        "league": "MLB",
        "city": "Houston"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "team_for_city",
      "question": "Which NBA team plays in Phoenix?",
      "options": [
        "Suns",
        "Wizards",
        "Grizzlies",
        "Cavaliers"
      ],
      "answer": "Suns",
      "meta": {
        "league": "NBA",
        "city": "Phoenix"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "city_for_team",
      "question": "In which city do the Nets play (NBA)?",
      "options": [
        "San Antonio",
        "Los Angeles",
        "Houston",
        "Brooklyn"
      ],
      "answer": "Brooklyn",
      "meta": {
        "league": "NBA",
        "team": "Nets"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "city_for_team",
      "question": "In which city do the Rockies play (MLB)?",
      "options": [
        "Colorado",
        "Minnesota",
        "Seattle",
        "St. Louis"
      ],
      "answer": "Colorado",
      "meta": {
        "league": "MLB",
        "team": "Rockies"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "team_for_city",
      "question": "Which MLB team plays in Los Angeles?",
      "options": [
        "Tigers",
        "Athletics",
        "Marlins",
        "Angels"
      ],
      "answer": "Angels",
      "meta": {
        "league": "MLB",
        "city": "Los Angeles"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "city_for_team",
      "question": "In which city do the Mariners play (MLB)?",
      "options": [
        "Detroit",
        "Seattle",
        "Los Angeles",
        "Boston"
      ],
      "answer": "Seattle",
      "meta": {
        "league": "MLB",
        "team": "Mariners"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "city_for_team",
      "question": "In which city do the Diamondbacks play (MLB)?",
      "options": [
        "Milwaukee",
        "Arizona",
        "Toronto",
        "Oakland"
      ],
      "answer": "Arizona",
      "meta": {
        "league": "MLB",
        "team": "Diamondbacks"
      }
    },
    {
      "type": "team_for_city",
      "question": "Which MLB team plays in Pittsburgh?",
      "options": [
        "Twins",
        "Cubs",
        "Pirates",
        "Reds"
      ],
      "answer": "Pirates",
      "meta": {
        "league": "MLB",
        "city": "Pittsburgh"
      }
    }
  ]
}